<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BMI Track Heart Rate Monitor</string>
    <string name="app_name2">BMI Track : Heart Rate Monitor</string>
    <string name="privacypolicy">Application is warning you about the app that gives you many services and important information for safer and efficient use.\n\nUser-Generated Content Policy(UGC) By pressing the Accept button, I declare I have read and accepted the following condition of use:</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use"><u>Terms and conditions of use</u></string>
    <string name="pp_p"><u>Privacy policy.</u></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="unit_kilogram">kg</string>
    <string name="unit_pounds">lb</string>
    <string name="unit_inches">ft</string>
    <string name="unit_centimeters">cm</string>
    <string name="version_1_0">Version : <font color="#80FFFFFF">1.0</font></string>
    <string name="actual_privacypolicy">We believe that privacy is important. We have created this policy to explain our privacy practices so that you can understand what information about you is collected, used and disclosed. We collect information from you to provide relevant service and a better user experience. With the consent of this privacy policy, your usage, statistics, input will be collected while using our application.\n\n  <b>Information Collection and Use</b> \n\nFor a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. \n\n <b>DEVICE PERMISSIONS</b>\n\n  HARDWARE.CAMERA \n CAMERA\n WAKE_LOCK\n INTERNET\n READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE\n WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE\n FOREGROUND_SERVICE\n\nWe use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of our Apps, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you to email messages and push notifications. We may also send you Service-related emails or messages (e.g., account verification, order confirmations, change or updates to features of our apps, technical and security notices). \n\n <b>Log Data</b>\n\nWe want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third-party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics. \n\n <b>Cookies</b>\n\nCookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory. This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third-party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.\n\n  <b>Service Providers</b>\n\n We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:\nTo facilitate our Service;\nTo provide the Service on our behalf;\nTo perform Service-related services;\nor To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.\nWe want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to their Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.\n\n  <b>Security</b>\n\nWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\n  <b>Links to Other Sites</b>\n\nThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. \n\n <b>Children’s Privacy</b>\n\nWe do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. We encourage all children to never submit any personally identifiable information through the Application and/or Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children\'s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide personally identifiable information through the Application and/or Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided personally identifiable information to us through the Application and/or Services, please contact us. You must also be at least 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your personally identifiable information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf). \n\n <b>Changes to This Privacy Policy</b>\n\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.\n\n  <b>Contact</b>\n\nYou can contact us about this privacy statement by writing an email to us.\n\n  <b>Thank You!</b></string>
    <string name="firebase_name">BmiTrackData</string>
</resources>